improved
Thank you for watching!
The third game is
Lilim
So that's it.
The third round is, right now, a little bit down below.
There is a white corner
The third game will be a game using this white corner.
You can use your legs and your whole body in this white corner.
There are a lot of games here.
Today we will play three games.
The first one is
No-Tray
No-tray
Speed rock-paper-scissors
Speed rock, paper, scissors
I pushed it.
It's going to start, so it's over.
This is Speed Rock-Paper-Scissors.
First, one person from each team goes out
And then we play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
One of the Guchoki pans
goes out on the ground.
Whoever picks the last one to go out first wins.
The first person to step on the rock-paper-scissors
the first person to step on the rock-paper-scissors with their foot
I'd like to do it.
I think it's very difficult to play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Yes, it is.
You have to use your head.
And you have to use your body, too.
It's a difficult game.
I'd like to try it.
Let's go!
Ending
First of all, this team is Karen, and this team is Yu! And this team is Yuu!
Please give my best regards to them.
Good luck! Come on!
Come on! I'll do my best!
I'll push. Yes, please.
I pressed it!
Pokey!
Go for it!
Oh, I'll do it!
Just win this.
Wow, Karen is so long.
No, you guys are totally in the league.
Really?
They're all full-length.
Which is which?
Karen's in a league of her own.
Wow!
We won!
We won?
I won! I'm the queen of speed rock-paper-scissors!
That was fast.
You're fast, Goyama.
How do you like it?
I love it.
It's very frustrating, but you can't help but get into the rhythm.
How did you like it?
Yes, I'm very happy to be the queen of speed rock-paper-scissors!
And it's cool.
You're not listening to me.
It was a good game.
It was pretty fast.
Very speedy.
You use either one? The head and the body.
I used my head.
I did.
I feel like I have better eyes.
It was a good match.
And now, let's move on to the second person...
Mon-chan and I are next. Mon-chan and I are next.
Mon-chan and Rine
I'd like to challenge the King of Whack-a-Mole!
It's really sad to beat Mr. Mole, but...
It's not an instinct.
Hime wouldn't do that.
She wouldn't do that.
Please do me a favor.
Let's do our best.
What is it, Hime?
Yes.
Yes, I'd like to beat them to the punch in a sexy way.
Please do your best.
Get down on your knees.
One, two, on your knees.
All right, let's start!
One at a time, the whack-a-mole game.
What shall we do?
That's good.
Oh, wow! That's great!
What? What? What?
Go, go, go, go!
That's great!
He's cute!
He's adorable!
Oh!
We won!
I lost!
That was hard.
That's why
My Sasaki Tournament
The winner is
The year is 2023!
Yay!
Year 2023 2023.
I'm sorry to hear that.
But now
It's one on one.
Next game.
We're going to win the championship.
Good, good, good.
Next game.
All four of us will try our hand.
This is the game.
Step race.
Step Race
This one is easy.
You have to step on something and
Carless is done
that is what it is called.
I understand.
Let's hear your enthusiasm.
Two teams at a time, please.
Yes, sir.
I don't think I have a car make.
But I'll do my best with my young legs.
Wow! I'm the one who said "I'm the one"!
I didn't say that. I didn't say that.
Well, then, we're adults, so we'll be sexy in a way that only adults can be sexy.
We won't be outdone by no-sexy.
We won't lose to no-sexy.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
Okay, let's go for the first ride.
Okay.
Yay!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
Let's do it!
What's this? Elmer!
Astélie?
Let's do it!
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
Wow!
You won!
Bummer.
Well, that was a great game.
Come on.
Neat. He's so frustrated.
Regretful, such a progression.
I'm taking a break, pretending to be frustrated
A good way to live
So, the step race
The winner is
Suddenly partitioned out
First place, Reine Kitamura
Congratulations!
I'm sorry to hear that, it's wonderful!
That's why,
I'll put my regrets in letters.
We played three games in the third round.
Um...
One break
We played three games in the third round
The winner is
Cecy.
So, that's why
This
Then, it's the last game.
Yay!
Now the winner is determined, the loser is determined, and it becomes frustrating. This determines the winner, which determines the loser, which becomes frustrating.
Regretful.
Let's do our best not to become regretful.
I will do my best.
Well then, let's go for the last time!
Go!
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Tastes like chocolate
It's got chocolate cookies in it.
Delicious!
Delicious
Yarinbo in appearance and in the mouth
Yummy.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I made it into a cheesecake
I chose cheesecake from the cake world.
Whenever I go to a cafe, I order cheesecake
Eight years have come and gone
Friendship is gorgeous
The final game is
Mick's Row.
Yay!
So we're in this dark space
New Sexy
Oh, sexy?
New Sexy members
Mixed Sexy
Yes, we put aside the sexy.
Let's leave the sexy aside.
Two members of each team will work together in the competition.
Yes, sir.
No sexy. No Sexy.
No sexy.
It's negative sexy.
Oh, no.
Oh, no?
Oh, my God.
We're gonna have to start working as a team.
There's a big screen here.
You can see the poses.
I see.
So we're going to follow the poses and work together as a team.
We'll work together as a team to create a pose
and make a pose together.
And then we're going to do a run.
I understand.
This is also a game of bonding and overcoming difficult poses
It's a game of bonding and overcoming challenges.
Yes, sir.
This is the latest chapter.
No matter if you cry or laugh
You'll die of frustration.
Don't you want to be frustrated?
I don't want to be frustrated anymore.
Yes, you do.
I don't want to be sorry.
I don't want to.
So
Let's do our best.
Let's do our best
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh!
Cute
Cute!
Go for it! It's the final battle! Put on the water! Sexy!
Let's get serious!
It's starting! Let's go! It's started! Come on!
Ooh! Good! Come on!
Is that a round?
Yes!
It's huge.
It's a big eXceration!
What's this?
I knew it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's deep inside.
It's good for couples. It's good for first dates.
Everybody's first date here.
I'm on fire.
Rats.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
Drink up, drink up, drink up
What is it?
I don't know
it's difficult
Ganbare ganbare
why why why
Oh, my God!
Did you see that?
Princess.
A princess.
What? What?
A dog.
It's a dog.
It even jumps!
I've seen it before.
That's good.
Grab him.
Get him.
Nice.
Jump jump jump. Jump Jump
No, absolutely.
It's on fire.
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't hurt yourself.
No, no, no, no.
You're gonna catch on fire.
What's this?
They'll see you holding it against the fire.
They'll see you.
Oh, my bone hurts.
Oh, it hurts, it hurts
That's nasty.
Oh, my God.
Aww.
Aah! Aah!
Uh...
something
Gulf Way
I don't know which way to look at it.
Oh, my God!
What's this?
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Oh, yeah! This one's kinda, you know, good.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
Shrimp, shrimp, shrimp, shrimp, shrimp, shrimp
If you're not in the mood...
That way! That way!
That way!
Good night.
Knees mer
There it is.
Oh, my gosh! Great!
OK!
That's a first!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Is that bad?
45625!
Oh, my God!
No. 4 and No. 2!
Good job, guys. That was super dangerous. Surprisingly. No, I think I did pretty well.
No, I really recommend this for a first date or something. No, it's not right if you come here as a couple.
You can go to Todotan. Thank you very much.
This was difficult. I'm tired.
This is great. This is amazing.
Amazing. But it was fun. I felt like I had a good workout.
I wanted to do that yoga pose. I wish I could have succeeded.
It's frustrating. Next time. Good luck.
A potential winner. Last.
45,000 something. 625?
You can pull off 60,000, right? Yes, that's right.
It's going to be a long fight. You've been doing it for quite a long time, haven't you? That's right.
It was for one song, right? That's more than that. More, huh?
Okay, I'll do my best. Let's do our best.
Last game. How's it going?
My stomach is starting to hurt. I'm getting nervous.
I'm nervous. But I don't want to feel frustrated.
I don't want to be. So, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. Okay, let's do it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Hey!
Go for it! Please.
Climb the pin pole on the footprints in the middle.
It was pretty hard. That's great.
My feet hurt quite a bit. More than I danced, because if you imagine just having fun, it takes a lot of energy.
Here we go. Go for it!
Oh! Good!
Good, good. Good, good.
Great, great. That's great.
Oh, takeo! That's cool. Ah, Takelo! Cool.
It's nice.
Ah.
Oh, here it is.
Oh, that's gonna be a grate.
Ah!
Yay!
Yeah!
I'm down! Cat and dog.
Mama.
Exelee.
Yay!
That's great. Quick.
Exerée.
Good. Good.
Goo.
Pearl.
Good.
Good. Good.
Goo.
Ha!
Ha! Good.
Hey, you're good.
Ha!
Ha! Ha!
Wow, it was 20,000 until now. It's 20,000.
I made a mistake.
Exelee.
Oh.
Ha!
Muscle man.
Exeray.
Ha!
New.
Oh, wow.
Ha! Ha!
Ha!
Go, go, go. That's great.
Go, go, go, go.
Oh, here it comes. Body core.
Core corner.
Break.
That's good.
Ha!
Oh, who wants to team up.
That's good.
I'd like to get tired from this point on.
I'm gradually losing my strength.
Please don't go over.
I don't want to feel frustrated.
Oh! Yeah!
Oh! Great!
No!
It's hard to jump.
Up!
That's funny.
Take it, take it, take it.
It's survival out here.
Good luck!
I learned a lot about English pronunciation.
Hibbard.
That didn't work.
It was pretty Japanese.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, my God. That's great.
Come on.
This is it.
What?
10,000 points to go.
What? Isn't that a lot?
Oh, no, no, no.
I've got a lot of energy left.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to be in a very frustrating situation.
What do I do?
I'm on four. What? I've only got about 5,000 left.
Oh, no!
What do I do?
I'm sorry, but I don't want to be that guy.
I'm here.
One more time.
Come on, please.
Come on.
Why don't you turn it up?
Okay.
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
That's good.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
A hundred, a thousand?
A thousand.
One thousand more.
1000 more?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
I've already lost.
What?
Did it drop?
Still down?
It's falling. It's falling.
Are you kidding me?
What? What?
Huh?
All together.
Jump.
Ready?
All right.
Good job, guys.
Get off.
I'll let you do this one
I'm gonna need you to do another one right here.
They're gonna add points.
They're not gonna give me points.
They're not gonna give you points.
Now that you're here, I'd like to see you increase your score.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I want you to beat your best score here.
Go for it.
I like it.
I can feel the bond between them.
Doggy, Cat, Hinano-chan
Lesson!
It's good!
Aizaru-jin?
He's kind of sideways.
Yes!
That's great! It's going on like crazy.
Ha!
Ooh!
Oh?
I'm in! I'm in!
Good!
Ah! You did it, too!
Ha!
Ha! Ha!
Aah!
You're so cute.
Yeah!
Oh!
Exe ne admire
I like it!
ahhhhh specialist move king mountain
Well then charmay
Too much fee, too صbit
I've been waiting for 2 years!
I'm buying it now!
It's a princess!
Wow!
You really should try it.
Ready, pen over!
What? Pen-over?
Oh!
Good job!
Hey, that's amazing! We're way over!
It's over 20,000!
That's amazing!
This is amazing!
Miyu's bangs have disappeared.
Where are Miyu's bangs?
All right, drink your water!
That was great!
It was great!
Hey! It was great!
I feel gravity!
I feel the gravity!
Good job!
We went through a lot of stuff.
It's true!
I've got a great shot.
I'm struggling to get through now.
I'm so tired. I was really tired, but...
It was a lot of fun.
Good, good, good.
I felt a little bit of everything.
Today's winners were
Kanagi Camp
What a buzz!
What's up with the giraffe?
Sexy
The main character this time is
previous work
Sumishiro
Tachibana
Growing up in camp
Thank you for watching!
Yay!
Yay.
Which one?
They get mixed up.
So, from the two winning teams
From the two members of the winning team
We, the candidates to win the 2023 JOYPOLICE Tournament...
We were eliminated last year.
It was 2024.
We didn't win that last year's tournament, but we
We could have.
In 2024, we did.
We made it, so we have the end of this year's
second semester
JOYPOLICE competition in the second semester.
Make sure you're ready.
Excuse me.
We're the team you fought with.
I'm so happy.
We will continue to do our best in the second semester of the JOYPOLICE Tournament.
You're off to a good start. Bye.
Thank you.Thank you.
I couldn't have done it without you.
So, we lost.
I'm so disappointed.
Next time there is a team, the name of the team will be the 2024 JOYPOLICE Tournament Champion
Indeed.
You said it's just like you hoped.
Yes, it is.
And I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Did you have a good time today?
It was fun.
I had so much fun.
Sounds like fun.
I haven't played yet.
There's a lot more than this that I'm really interested in.
I wish I could come to Kenny's.
I want to come.
We should all come.
There's so much to see and do!
Please come and visit us!
Today
Today we visited JOYPOLICE Leon Sendai Nakayama Store!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
I hope you all come and visit us.
Let's wait!
It was fun!
Dogs
Cats